NO ANIMALS WERE HARMED DURING
THE FILMING OF THIS PRODUCTION
Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com
Open up! Trusting a Turk?
A woman! Trusting a Cuman woman!
Faltyos was right. My dear friend!
They imprisoned you!
I need more soldiers.
I need more weapons!
I need to push Osman and
his Alps into an open field.
Then in one move…
… in one move, I’ll
take all of them down.
No tricks. No games.
No mysteries!
Rome against Turks. Osman
against Nikola! That’s how it will happen.
Yes. Exactly like this!
I’ll crush them down
with a well-armed army, but!
But! There are no
soldiers Rome can give me!
Is that it?
Unfortunately.
Okay. How will I beat
that shepherd then? How?
The Holy Emperor thought
you knew the answer to that.
Did this guy just criticise me?
The Emperor…
Either he’ll find soldiers for me,
or I’ll get them from Geyhatu!
But I will find them!
Selamun Aleykum [Peace be with you]
Father!
I’ll make these lands you’ve conquered…
… the lands of the Turks!
In the eyes of the oppressed…
I’ll be hope, not tears.
I’ll be the nightmare of the cruel!
Now…
With the prayers of
the oppressed from all religions…
… all over these lands…
… I’ll expand my borders.
My ancestor Oghuz Khan…
My grandfather Suleiman Shah…
… and you…
I’ll be worthy of your bloodline, and
your traditions.
Today is the day of
the Bey council, father.
May Allah, not let us down.
Let’s hope for the best.
Selamun Aleykum. [Peace be with you]
Aleykum Selam. [Peave be with you too]
Where do you come from,
where do you go to?
We came from Aleppo
to Söğut to trade, my Bey.
Merchant Abdullah Bin Malik.
I used to be his slave.
Now I’m his son.
I’ve heard that our mighty Ertuğrul
Bey who saved my life has passed away.
In fact, the reason I came here
was to ask for his blessings.
My father had told me.
Your caravan got attacked
by the Mongols while you were here.
My father protected your
lives and your goods. Is that correct?
Your father?
Are you Osman Bey,
the son of Ertuğrul Bey?
Osman Bey!
If you allow me, my valiant,
I’d like to give you a hug!
Sorry for your loss.
May our Ertuğrul Bey rest in peace.
Thank you.
I see the light of your
father in your eyes, son.
But…
Those who attacked
my caravan weren’t Mongols.
They were the soldiers
of Lord Vasilius.
Then, welcome to Söğüt,
Melik Bin Abdullah.
Thank you.
What about you?
I was freed from the oppression
of the cruel, thanks to Ertuğrul Bey.
After seeing that I had no one,
your father gave me a name.
May he rest in peace.
He granted me his father's name.
Süleiman.
Not just a name,
he gave me a father...
... and three valiant brothers,
far from home.
Thanks to my Allah that
I'm before Osman Bey, my brother.
Welcome, brother!
Thank you.
Be my guest at the inn.
Now, your lives and
goods are safe with Kayı.
And Kayı Tent is now your homes.
May Allah bless you, Osman Bey.
If you become the Bey...
... may you be
the hope of the world of Islam...
... with many conquest
in your father's path.
It's time, my Savcı.
It's time you keep
your promise to me and Kayı.
Now go and show
those Beys what a Kayı Bey is.
I'll be waiting for good news from you.
Don't worry, Hatun.
There is no other possibility.
I'll be chosen the Bey
and everyone will have to accept it.
This took too long
and I'm out of patience.
After you're the Kayı's Bey,
I'll be their Hatun.
While you're putting
the Beys in their places...
... I'll put Selcan and Bala to theirs.
And of course, get my revenge
from Aygül who drew her sword to me.
Everthing will be accounted for.
One by one.
Boran Alp! Time of the meeting is close.
Say what you have to say.
I want to talk about this meeting.
My brother Göktuğ
and I are competent in battle.
We fight by our Osman Bey's side.
You also know that we were
victorious with Osman Bey many times.
We saw enemy's armies
scatter, their castles fall.
We know that if Osman Bey wasn't here,
we would have gotten those victories.
Now, Kayı will be victorious many
times only if Osman Bey becomes the Bey.
We want you to think
about this during the council.
You did everything that suited you.
And we'll do everything that suits us.
What is it that suits you?
This isn't right, Boran Alp.
This isn't the place where
we announce our Bey.
Excuse us.
Take care of yourselves.
They didn't say anything.
- I hope they got the message.
- Inshallah.
Let's go.
It is time we become a state!
I'll show you how one
becomes a state, Osman Bey.
Tell me how you will show him
so that I can also be happy, Dündar Bey.
Today, I'll become the Bey.
How?
What are you saying, Dündar Bey?
How will that happen?
What did you do?
May I enter, my Bey?
Come in, Saltuk.
My Bey, I've completed your order.
Tell us what you did so
that Hazal Hatun knows them.
Come on.
As you ordered, I've handed
out the gold to the Beys.
They promised to vote for you today.
You may leave, Saltuk.
My Bey!
What have you done?
This isn't a job for Savcı, Hatun.
I saw that he can't take care of Osman.
I won't wait for them to fight each other.
I'll be the Bey right away.
My lion! My man!
Head of my Tent!
May you be an honored Bey.
I'll wait for the news.
I'll wait to take our revenge.
I'll wait, to celebrate
all day and all night.
My mighty creator...
... show me that moment.
Oh, Dündar Bey!
Alps. Is everything ready?
Did you complete your duties?
We have, my Bey.
But there's something new.
Dündar Bey bribed three voters, my Bey.
With gold, my Bey.
He asked them to support him.
Uncle...
So, he also deceived
my brother Savcı.
How did you find this out?
Saltuk. Don't be
shy brother, tell us.
Dündar Bey...
I'm thankful of Dündar
Bey for lots of things. He trusted me.
But he gave up acting like a Kayı Bey.
Saltuk. Tell us brother.
What did Dündar Bey do?
He wanted me
to hand gold out to Beys.
They'll vote Dündar Bey.
He bribed all
the Beys except for the Blacksmith.
Look at that Dündar Bey!
Thank you, brother.
You should go.
Don't mention this to anyone else.
We'll tell Osman Bey about this.
That what he said, huh? I'd love
to strangle my uncle and expose this.
But then, they will
know that Saltuk spoke.
We shall wait.
If that's the case, my Bey, we
should crush the Beys who took bribes!
Slow down, Gence Bey. Don't rush it.
We'll get through this
with our minds, not anger.
May I enter, my Bey?
Come in, Dumrul.
Selamun Aleykum.
[Peave be with you]
Aleykum Selam.
[Peace be with you too]
My Bey, Cerkutay
wants your permisson to come here.
Let him come.
What are you doing here on
the day of council, Cerkutay?
There will be chaos if
they don't choose you as a Bey.
I thought you'd need manpower.
What about they choose
me as a Bey?
I thought then, there
would be a feast!
Alps! Do you see this?
No one but Allah
can see who is on whose side.
Think about a solution for this thing.
As you order, my Bey.
Welcome, brother.
Selamun Aleykum.
- Aleykum Selam.
I've been waiting for you
for days, Melik Bin Abdullah. Welcome.
I believe you are the potter
İdris whom I'll be collaborating with.
Correct. I've placed your men to the inn.
They all are comfortable, thankfully.
Good. We've visited
Ertuğrul Ghazi's grave and prayed.
May Allah accept it.
We've also met
Osman Bey in the mean time.
- We will be his guests.
- Good.
The light in his eyes
reminded me of his father.
It does, it does.
Let me take you to your rooms.
The truth comes to
light after doors are closed.
Let there be light.
And God said, "Let there be light,"
and there was light.
Powerful and free.
I bless your aweakening from
the darkness, my brother David.
I have been reborn on the
arms of the holy Father, Master Petrus.
How did you convince Osman Bey
that you were his father's old friends?
He didn't believe us at first.
He gave us wrong
information to trick us.
Your caravan was attacked
by Mongols while you were in Söğüt.
My father protected your
lives and your goods. Right?
After Ertuğrul saved you and this gimp...
... who attacked your caravan? Mongols?
... Lord Vasilius and his soldiers.
What about you, David? Could you get
the information the Father asked you to?
I think Ertuğrul gave his
plans to a brother figure before he died.
- He might have what you are looking for.
- Who?
Bamsı. Bamsı Bey.
After Ertuğrul got sick.
Bamsı was nowhere to be seen for a while.
He appeared out of nowhere one day.
But he kept disappearing
from the Tent secretly.
Do you know where he goes to?
He lost me at the Mount
Abdalan's foot everytime.
Oh, the Sultan of the Ghazis!
Here are your relics!
I remember the things you said while
trusting me with these like yesterday.
"My Bamsı!", you said to me.
"Protect these as if
they were your honour!"
I did, my Bey.
I protected them like my honour!
Now, it's time I deliver
these to your successor.
It is time these are in
the hands of the new Bey.
Inshallah, the Bey elected,
will be Osman Bey.
Allah forbid if it is someone else...
... we're doomed.
Today in Kayı Tent...
... both Kayı's and the world of Turks'
future will be determined.
And that is what these relics tell.
Oh, the ancestor of all Ghazis...
Oh, the Sultan of Ghazis.
My beautiful Bey...
I need to be at the council of Beys
on time. I need to get going. Excuse me.
Good.
Now go and
learn who the new Bey is.
Bamsı will take us and
the new Bey to the secret spot.
I'll go to see Lord Nikola.
I don't want to go empty handed.
You'll send a gift to him.
As you order, Master Petrus.
You'll kidnap Flatyus
from the tent tonight.
Is everything read, uncle?
Don't worry, nephew. I spoke to
them again. All of them will support you.
This will end today.
I hope Osman accepts it peacefully.
If he denies the Beys' decisions,
neither will Bamsı.
They have to accept it.
If they don't, no one will support them.
We'll crush their words!
Gündüz, my son.
May he rest in peace.
You know the lion which sleeps
inside Ertuğrul Bey's heart, don't you?
I know, Bamsı Bey.
Then you also know who
the Kayı's future belongs to, son.
The future of Kayı.
We'll wait and see, Bamsı Bey.
Selamın Aleykum.
Aleykum Selam, son.
Come.
Take it, son.
Son...
With Allah's permission...
You will enter this tent as my son...
... and you'll exit as my Bey, Inshallah.
Inshallah, Bamsı Bey.
You already know who
I'll vote for, Osman Bey.
When it's my time to talk, I'll
speak a few extra words.
Thank you.
Let's go then.
Hunter of lions, Flatyos!
Do you go outside
without your Osman Bey?
Have fun while you can.
Since these are your last moments.
Do you think I fear death?
You're scared like a dog!
Your words don't matter.
Your eyes tell the truth.
After the council of Beys ends, we'll
make you choose your death.
Will your Bey win the voting?
He will.
Then we'll attack all your castles.
First İnegöl, then Yayılhisar!
Then İznik! And even Bursa!
Brothers! The council is about to begin.
Let's go, my Boran.
Let's go.
After I get out of here...
I'll make all of you pay for this.
With the name of Allah.
With Allah's 99 name...
...who creates everything...
...who fills our hearts with faith.
Al-Fatihah for the soul of...
...the late Ertuğrul Ghazi.
Beys of the Kayı...
...I welcome you all,
one by one.
Thank you.
As the eldest bey of the Kayı...
...I'm responsible for managing
this meeting.
Beys, the late Ertuğrul Bey's
three sons...
...and his one brother can claim
the position of bey...
...according to our traditions.
May Allah bless our decision,
and help us choose the best.
Amin.
Beys of the Kayı,
I wish that...
...you will not forget whose position
we are choosing someone.
But I still want to remind it.
The late Ertuğrul Ghazi...
...didn't rule like a bey...
...Ertuğrul Ghazi ruled like a sultan.
He didn't say that he didn't
have soldiers...
...that he can't do it with
a few ghazis...
...he said that he ruled the most
noble tribe of Oghuzs.
He ruled that way.
The beys of Kayı...
...the flag of Kayı can't be lowered
from where Ertuğrul Ghazi raised it.
A bey who doesn't
trust in...
...himself or in his tribe...
...who is afraid of freedom,
who bows to Rums or Mongols...
...can't rule this tribe.
This should be known, and decisions
should be made based on this.
Dündar Bey.
You are the first to speak.
Tell us.
Bamsı Bey is right.
Three nephews of mine and I are
candidates.
I want to give up on my claim and
support one of those three brothers.
But I don't know which
one will I pick.
Whichever I choose, I'll hurt the others,
I said.
And by doing the most appropriate...
...I held my right...
...and voted for myself.
I'm a candidate.
Thank you, Dündar Bey.
Sülemiş Bey. It's your turn.
I see the future of the Kayı...
...in the late Ertuğrul Ghazi's
son, Osman Bey.
My candidate is Osman Bey.
Thank you.
Bala, my girl, I didn't like the color of
the fabrics.
Don't worry, mother.
Just like that, Targun, my girl.
Kayı women should always be working.
You'll learn too.
-Of course, I will.
-Well.
Lena, you are acting weird today.
What's wrong?
Am I acting weird, Hazal Hatun? As the
meeting day came closer, you turned weider.
I'm excited that Savcı Bey will win.
You are a bit too excited.
I'm excited because we will win...
...but why are they happy?
Are they excited for losing, I wonder?
Mother, don't hold me back.
Let me cut her tongue.
Or let me stitch it so that she
can never speak again.
Aygül, why is the hurry, my girl?
What will she do when Osman
becomes the bey?
She will sit and eat her tongue
bit by bit.
Well, what do they say...
...hope is the bread of the poor...
...they say.
-Bala!
-Aygül! Aygül!
Aygül, stop!
Aygül!
Enough, enough!
-Enough!
-Aygül!
Aygül, come with us.
Aygül!
So, Targun, my girl. Tell us, you are
silent. Are you all right?
I'm fine, Selcan Hatun. Thank you.
I'm waiting for the results, like everyone else.
Soon, my girl.
Inshallah. Soon.
-Sinan Bey, it's your turn.
-Thank you.
My vote is for Dündar Bey, who I believe
that will act by his mind.
Thank you.
Gündüz Bey, tell us.
It's your turn.
I won't act like my uncle.
I won't mind who gets upset.
The future of the Kayı...
...it's obvious who has
the future of the Kayı.
He who conquered Kulucahisar twice...
...he who saved Söğüt...
...he who...
...saved my uncle and
my brother...
...from Nikola...
...is the bey of the Kayıs.
I'm Gündüz Bey.
I give up on my claim.
I give my vote for my brother Osman,
who deserves to be the bey of the Kayı.
Gündüz Bey, thank you.
Cafer Bey, tell us.
-My vote is for Dündar Bey.
-Thank you.
Thank you. Thank you.
Osman Bey.
It's your turn now.
Tell us.
My words are on...
...the walls of Kulucahisar.
And it will be on the walls of
İnegöl and Larhisar.
My intentions are clear.
I'll conquer distant lands...
...and I'll make the Kayı strong.
And it is obvious what I need
for this...
...and who I vote for.
Thank you, Osman Bey.
Now, Dündar Bey has three votes...
...and Osman Bey has three votes.
Sevindik Bey, who do you vote for?
I vote for Dündar Bey.
Thank you.
Davud Bey, tell us.
My vote is as obvious as
Osman Bey's.
For Osman Bey to accomplish
what...
...he said that he will...
...my vote is for Osman Bey
Thank you, Davud Bey.
Thank you.
İdris Bey, it's your turn.
Who do you vote for?
My vote is for Dündar Bey, who I trust
in his experience and wit.
I want him to be the Bey of the Kayıs.
Thank you.
Thank you, İdris Bey.
Beys of the Kayı. Dündar Bey has
five votes, Osman Bey has four votes.
Two votes are left...
...so, it is impossible for Gündüz Bey
or Savcı Bey to get elected.
My vote is for, obviously...
...Osman Bey.
Now, the votes are equal.
Savcı Bey, it's your turn.
What you will say will determine
the bey of the Kayı.
Look at this brother of mine...
...who steps over me...
...who shakes me off...
...who hits me,
who shouts at me...
...who tells me to back off.
My brother.
Now, am I...
...supposed to give my vote
for him..
...and elect him?
And my uncle.
Only he supported me on this cause...
...told me that he supported me,
he saw me worthy of the position.
Now, can I...
...look directly into his eyes....
...and choose someone else?
Can I let someone else be the bey?
I can't deceive anyone...
...looking directly into their eyes...
...but my uncle can.
Now look at my uncle
who lied to me,...
....looking
directly into my eyes...
...who deceived me,
who stabbed me on my back!
My nephew, maybe it's a misunderstanding.
-Of course, I--
-So, you want to be the Bey?
So, you want to be the bey, uncle?
So, you talked to some people secretly
to convince them.
Savcı! Know what you say!
Know what you say!
Dündar Bey!
Savcı Bey!
This is the election of the bey.
Savcı Bey, sit back.
Savcı Bey, tell us.
Who do you vote for?
The bey of the Kayı will
be determined by your word.
Then, then...
...everyone should listen to me well...
...I rather have a
knife on my neck...
...than a neck on my back.
...I rather the one who roars to myself,
than the one who hisses behind my back.
I rather have some dreamer
ruin the future of the Kayı...
...than a liar decaying it to dust.
I...
...Savcı Bey...
...give my vote for...
...my brother Osman.
Now, whether we'll fight with Mongols
or Rums...
...or both...
...will be decided by him.
We should die but...
...shouldn't crawl.
From now on, with the
votes of the beys...
...Süleyman Shah's son Ertuğrul Ghazi's
son Osman Bey...
...is the new bey of the Kayı tribe.
May Allah make him victorious.
Amin.
Wait there, uncle!
A bey can't be elected like this!
I'll never accept the title which
is gained like this.
It's apparent that some people
are bought by gold.
And some were promised
for the title.
But they were deceived.
Beys, we are electing a bey of Kayı!
A bey of Kayı is the embodiment
of the will of the people.
Put your hand to your heart.
Can an election be like this?
And the other votes for someone else
because he is mad at the other.
Someone who accept to be elected like
this, can't rule the Kayıs.
And he shouldn't!
When a bey of Kayı gets elected,
when our children ask us, what will we say?
Tell us, what will we say?
Is this the foundation of the
state that we will form?
Is this the first work of the generation
that dreams of great conquests?
Is this our cause?
Tell me.
I...
...Ertuğrul Ghazi's son...
...Osman Bey.
For the state that I will form,
for the cities that I will conquer...
...for the great civilization that
I await...
...I want you to choose me because
I am worthy.
Bamsı Bey.
Votes should be recounted.
Thank you, my valiant.
Beys.
Let's do it.
Now, this is the situation.
Those who vote for Osman Bey...
...should raise their hands.
Now it's done.
May it bring good.
Where are you going to, uncle?
What is the hurry?
Don't you have a duty to hand over?
What is it?
What duty?
Aren't you the governor of Söğüt
that got attacked twice...
...and that you were incapable to defend
at first, and left at second.
-Yes, I am.
-Not anymore.
I resign you.
If you allow me, may I get out...
...Osman Bey.
Leave in peace.
And about you, brother...
...as the leader of the alps,
during the conquest of Kulucahisar...
...while Söğüt was
getting saved, where were you?
Tell us, where were you, brother?
If you are in silence...
...if you accept your incapability...
...then, I resign
you from your duty.
Very well, brother.
Very well.
If you allow me, Osman Bey.
As you want, Savcı Bey.
Osman...
...my dark Osman.
Osman Bey...
...now, the new bey of the Kayıs,
Osman Bey.
Bamsı Bey.
O' people!
The election is over!
The new bey of the Kayıs...
...is Ertuğrul Ghazi's son...
...Osman Bey!
Brother!
Thank Allah!
The new bey of the Kayıs is
Ertuğrul Ghazi's son, Osman Bey!
God damn it!
Dündar was going to play with Savcı,
it seems that Savcı played him first.
If you allow me.
Go to your bey.
Come on.
Thank Allah, Bala.
Thank Allah Thank Allah.
-Thank Allah.
-Mother Gonca, thank Allah.
Thank Allah.
Osman Bey...
...is much more powerful now.
The new bey of the Kayıs is
Ertuğrul Ghazi's son, Osman Bey!
So, you don't want the war to end, huh?
So, you want to be destroyed by the Mongols?
So you want to die, huh?
I'll drown you in your blood!
Abdurrahman Ghazi, tell me what you will.
I'm curious.
What's this?
What's this, Abdurrahman Ghazi?
This is the will of our Ertuğrul Ghazi.
My Ertuğrul Bey...
With the name of Allah.
Abdurrahman Ghazi,
he wants Osman to be the bey...
...that's what it says.
Why didn't he say that?
-I asked that question, Bamsı Bey
-What did he say?
He said that he will follow our
holy prophet.
He didn't leave an heir, he said.
I want him to be elected by the beys,
by the people, he said.
He wanted Osman to be elected
with the support of the people.
He didn't want anyone...
...to stand against him and say ''You
wouldn't be the bey if Ertuğrul Bey...
...hadn't told us so!''
Brother, if that was the case...
...why did he put it to his will?
-As a measure, brother. As a measure.
If someone makes a scheme...
...you will reveal it
and show to the beys, he said.
So, Osman will get his right, he said.
Abdurrahman Ghazi...
...his will isn't just about that.
You have visitors, sir.
Petros.
I know you.
What are you doing in my castle?
And what are you after? May I learn?
Is this how you greet an old friend,
Nikola?
A friend?
A friend? A friend, huh?
Osman had hurt you a bit, it seems.
Petros.
You are in the lands of the empire.
Know your place.
After all, we don't look kindly
to the men of the pope.
And also, the people who pillaged
Constantinople are less favorable...
...for us than the people
who took Kulucahisar.
The enemy of my enemy...
...is my friend.
In here, I decide who is a friend
and who is an enemy.
Now, why are you here?
Pope Nicholaus Quartus?
What does your holy pope...
...want from Osman, Petros?
-Same thing with you.
He wants to end him.
Petros. Why would your holy pope
be so interested in someone so far away?
He doesn't want him to get closer one day.
He wants him to stay away forever.
And if possible, he wants him to die
as soon as possible.
So, the pope has ears in Söğüt.
As he has in everywhere. Turkic armies
should never unite under him.
Because that would
be so dangerous.
That would be so dangerous that we can't
trust in you and sit at our homes then.
We have to support you.
Gentlemen, to work around here,
ears around enough.
You need weapons.
You know it well that
we have the effective weapons.
The ears you hid,
I mean the weapons...
...should stay
where they are.
Because I don't need them.
So, you don't need us?
All right.
-Where is your right-hand Flatyos?
-Haven't your ears in Söğüt told you?
They have, wouldn't they? We even started
our preparations to save him but...
-Saving him from the Kayı Tribe?
-As a sign of our good intentions.
But if you don't need us.
Very well.
Let's do it like this.
If you can save Flatyos from
the Kayı Tribe, safe and sound.
Then, I'll see what I can
do with you.
Is that all right?
When Flatyos returns to your castle,
safe and sound...
...you'll see what we can do.
Then...
...you'll learn how to show respect.
Matmazel.
Stay with us for the dinner!
How considerate they are, Helen.
They took all that way to help me.
Do you think that I look that dumb?
What are their real intentions?
They are after a greater hunt.
I have to find that out.
We are partners in killing Osman.
And about the great hunt,
I like great hunts.
You do. Should I sent
men after them?
Helen, dear Helen.
Shouldn't you have acted...
...already, thinking that
I would like that?
Helen?
Things will go crazy.
A lot.
Existence and nothingness...
...the truth is unity,
and unity is the state.
Hail our bey!
This gate is the gate of the state!
It can't be forced!
It can't get broken by wits!
It requires a heart!
Our state shall live long!
The sword you're carrying is not yours!
The horse you are riding is not yours!
The throne you are sitting on is not yours!
Time is not yours!
Your position is not yours!
The path you are taking is not yours!
Your dreams is not yours!
- They're all for our community!
- Thanks to Turkish people!
Long live Osman Bey!
Osman Bey.
This Beyhood is Oghuz Khan's tradition.
This is Alparslan's soul,
Kilicarslan's faith...
Süleiman Shah's blood, Ertugrul Ghazi's
heritage.
May your Beyhood be blessed.
May your Beyhood be blessed!
Thank you Bamsı Bey.
Thank you.
Osman Bey, connect with the tradition.
You shall be wise, you shall listen to
your heart.
You shall carry on the tradition!
You shall carry on our state!
You shall lead our people!
From now on state is yours.
Long live our state!
Osman Bey, son of Ertugrul Ghazi.
Do not forget the oath you took.
Always remember you are just a creature
of the creator who is the owner of...
doomsday, the Lord of the universe.
Osman Bey, this sword is
Suleiman Shah's son...
Ertugrul Ghazi's sword.
You are going to carry it now. You are
going to be the commander of Ghazis.
May Allah bless you.
Amen!
Osman Bey, you shall carry our banner to
the castles...
and other lands, other cities.
Amen!
Thank you my Lord.
Thank you.
O' the almighty, filling our hearts
full of faith...
with Allah's all 99 name.
From now on, I took over
the throne.
I took my sword.
Now, it's time to unite...
unite and be a state!
From now on, we are going to celebrate
lots of conquests we're going to carry out!
New conquests will bring new victories...
and Kayı's banner is going to land on
the other lands!
Inshallah.
Be fair, you are going to be
treated in a fair way.
Try hard, you are going to
find help.
Be patient, you are going to
be freed.
My Ghazis, my Ahis, my sisters...
my brothers!
We are going to found a different state.
We are going to leave our children
our effort...
our passion, our justice.
Until...
We spread our names and banner
to the four winds...
and be the hope for oppressed
all around the world...
Let them be hopeful, because we're coming!
Don't be jealous.
Be gratitude.
Don't be lazy.
Be hardworking.
Don't be affected.
Be effective.
Don't be tricky!
Be honourable.
Judicious judges,
Fredom fighter soldiers...
and merchants with work ethics.
We need these people.
We need to write grand books,
we need to produce grand ideas...
we need to be grand.
We need to build grand...
grand madrasahs.
And live long!
This is what history wants our people...
to do so.
No doubt that this is the right way.
Allah-u Akbar!
(Allah is the greatest!)
To the to be Sultan of ours...
Al-fatiha!
My Allah, grant our master...
help our master Muhammed and his ummah.
"I seek help from Allah to protect me
against banished devil"
"In the name of Allah, the merciful,
compassionate"
So, know ˹well, O Prophet,˺ that there is no god
˹worthy of worship˺ except Allah. (Muhammad 47:19)
La ilahe illallah.
(there is no god except for Allah)
-Arabic hymn-
Whenever you see a heartbroken one...
be balm for them.
Be the helper of oppressed...
when they are stranded.
-his name is glorious-
Our state shall rise...
Our brave men will glorify us.
We run away from the ones...
who seek selfishness.
Oh, oh...
Our prophet was the leader of the
oppressed.
Wander around, search for the oppresseds
to help them...
like Mustafa (prophet Muhammed)
Don't let us be worker of
this mortal world.
So that we can work for afterlife.
Haji Ahmad...
Haji Ahmad died in hamartia.
Oh what a pity, what a longing.
Don't let us die without
remembering your name.
For the sake of almighty trees...
honor us with your power.
We pray, we pray for...
your name.
For your name.
Al-Rahman, al-rahim.
(the merciful, the compassionate)
Illallah!
(ending)
illahu!
Allah Allah!
Beloved Allah!
˹He will also give you˺ another favour
that you long for: help from Allah...
and an imminent victory. ˹ ˹So˺ give good
news ˹O Prophet˺ to the believers.
(As-saf 61:13)
Allah the first, Allah the last, Allah the
evident, Allah the obscure.
There's no God but Allah, and Muhammed
is his messenger.
Evilness shall leave, goodness, shall
arrive.
May Allah grant us happiness.
May rebels be ruined.
Our sins shall be forgiven.
Our last words shall be shahada.
May our Ertugrul Bey Ghazi be blessed.
May he rest in peace.
May our Osman Bey's new role be praised.
May his sword be sharp.
May he be wise.
May he be the conquerer.
May our martyred ones be blessed.
May our state live long.
May our people be happy forever.
May our enemies go down.
- Praying in Arabic -
Ya Allah!
Savcı! Savcı!
How could you do that?
How could you give the Beyhood to Osman?
Savcı! How?!
You keep shouting.
If you were patient and didn't
change your mind at the last moment...
Beyhood would be yours!
Hatun! Enough.
Now isn't the time. Enough!
My stupid mind! Ah!
How could I trust you?
I said enough! Don't you understand? Huh?
Enough! Don't you understand?
Don't you understand!
Don't you understand?
I said enough! Now isn't the time!
Tell me!
- Can I come in, my Bey?
- No, tell me!
- Osman Bey is waiting for you.
- Tell him I won't come!
I won't come!
Now, you know you
shouldn't touch an angry man.
Now, you know.
Osman...
- My Bala.
- My Osman.
My Osman Bey.
My Allah accepted my prayers.
My heart wouldn't want
another man as Kayı Bey.
My Bala.
Now, you'll be the head of Kayı Hatuns.
However...
your job more difficult.
Why, my Osman?
I know how to hold
Dündar Bey and Brother Savcı.
However, how will
you hold Hazal and Lena Hatun?
Don't worry, Selcan Hatun will do that.
Listen to Selcan Hatun's advices.
She'll tell you some things tonight.
Osman Bey!
Targun Hatun and İnal Bey
want to come in.
They will say something.
Come in.
- I congratulate your Beyhood.
- Thank you, İnal Bey.
Sit, please.
Aunt Selcan.
My Osman Bey.
Sit, please.
You saved me.
I owe you.
You gave up on your freedom
by not attacking us.
It's our duty to save you.
I heard you'll marry my daughter Targun.
Having a relationship between
Cumans and Kayıs...
is the right thing.
Be our guest tonight too.
We'll talk about it later.
Yes.
We should make a wedding.
Osman Bey.
I talked to my father. I'll be a Muslim.
Are there anything to stop me?
No, of course.
We should hurry.
My Aunt Selcan will teach you...
the Shahada and Islam's basic rules.
Of course.
As long as you want to learn.
I do.
Excuse us, Osman Bey.
Of course.
Targun Hatun is till playing, Osman Bey.
My Bala, Aunt Selcan is going to tell
you something.
I'll go and check the Alps.
Come, daughter.
So...
Savcı.
Yes, Uncle.
So, you prefer Osman.
So, you deceive Beys and use them.
You've deceived me!
You've done things behind my back!
I don't deceive any Bey.
They don't want you to become a Bey, then.
You haven't received any vote.
You haven't been able to say your name.
So...
why did you want to become a Bey?
I had to!
I prevented Osman
endanger the Beyhood.
You?
Why did you want to become a Bey?
It doesn't matter now.
You say Osman will endanger
the Beyhood.
Now, the problem is...
will we stop it or watch it happen?
So, we should move together.
You want me to believe your lies again!
Don't believe if you don't want to.
Do whatever you want.
Then, Geyhatu may cut our heads off.
What will we do
when they capture Kayı's Hatuns...
when they kill Kayı's children...
when they burn your father's tent?
We should unite!
You should've thought about
that before you deceived me.
Before you prevented my Beyhood.
Now, bear the consequences.
My beautiful daughter.
My Osman should've been a Bey, now he is.
You should've been Hatun of Bey, now
you are.
I should've told you some things, here
I am.
My mother.
I'm listening.
You know I will never forget what you say.
Mashaallah.
Bala Hatun, Hatun of Bey, listen to me.
Hatuns of Turk Beys are important.
Hatuns take care of the tent when
their Beys are away.
You'll be Osman's eyes when he is away.
You'll treat everyone mercifully.
Listen to their
complaints carefully, daughter.
Yes, mother. I'll listen to you.
However...
Don't tell your
Bey if you hear bad wishes.
Don't make your Bey' mind busy...
for wishes that are not right.
If someone wants something
right, treat them rightfully.
If someone wants you to be injustice...
reject them and warn them.
Yes, mother. I'll listen to you.
Bala Hatun, daughter of Sheikh
Edebali, Hatun of Bey...
The advice
I give to you aren't right anymore.
You know how to talk, how
to stay silent...
where to walk and where to stop.
Do however you want.
Mother.
Selcan Mother.
- Thank you so much.
- Thank you, daughter.
Are you fine? Tell me.
Yes, mother. Thank Allah.
However...
I don't know what Targun Hatun is up to.
Tell me what should I do.
We'll take our revenge, daughter.
We'll take revenge from those who
did this to us as I promised.
We owe to Osman Bey.
We pay his favors back sooner or later.
Yes father.
I'll be closer to Osman Bey for us.
I'll be the head of my Beylic. (Beyhood)
I'll gather my Alps again.
Our raids will collapse Roman.
I'll destroy them.
I'll help you, father.
I'll be your sharpest sword.
We'll have Kayıs' power.
Are you sure you want to...
marry Osman Bey?
I'll marry him.
I'll be his Hatun.
Do whatever you say.
We'll be relatives with Kayıs.
Kayı and Cuman blood will be mixed.
A new descent will come from you.
My grandchildren will be Beys of Kayıs.
They will be, father.
Don't worry.
I saw them all, son.
I saw you, I saw our Beylic.
I saw horizons.
I saw everything.
Tell me about the others.
The war fire is close.
This fire will burn...
until it is gone.
I won't stop then.
Kayı will grow up.
Grow up.
Kayı's enemies will grow up.
We'll have so many enemies...
like Nikola.
The ruler in Constantinople
will come here.
Father.
We don't have time.
We should set a new way.
We should be organized again.
Say what you'll say.
Don't keep it inside you.
I will say it.
I will.
However, I'm afraid of what I'll hear.
Savcı Bey...
did you choose Osman?
My uncle deceived me, Lena.
You warned me many times but I didn't
listen to you.
He bought Beys for himself.
Whether my Uncle was going to be Bey...
or Osman.
I preferred Osman.
You preferred Osman.
You preferred Bala to Hazal!
- So, I have to obey Bala!
- Lena!
Stop thinking about yourself.
Our Beylic is under a threat.
Osman's greed and desperateness will
endanger us!
You should've thought that earlier.
Can I come in?
My Bayhoca.
Mother.
- Mother.
- Son!
I came to you.
Welcome, son.
I wish I came earlier.
Let me look at you.
I missed you so much.
Father.
- Welcome, son. My son.
- Father.
My brave son.
Father, thank Allah that my uncle
Osman has become Bey.
You've voted for him.
That's nice.
I'm so proud as your son.
Of course my uncle Osman should be Bey.
His brother Savcı Bey knows that, I said.
From now on...
my brother Göktuğ is the Head of Alps.
Your command, my Bey.
Thank you.
My brother Boran...
will come with me.
He'll be with me wherever I go.
Only he'll know my secrets.
- Your command, my Bey.
- Thank you.
My uncle and my brother...
they didn't come to...
any of my ceremony.
Apparently...
they will stand up to my Beyhood.
Watch them.
Thank you, my Bey.
About Flatyos...
because of what he did to Beys of Kayı...
he'll be hanged tomorrow.
That Nikola dog will also
be hanged when I have him.
Eat all of them.
- You'll be hanged soon.
- You're right.
I shouldn't go to the other side hungry.
Is there wine?
Is it for that dog?
- Inshallah, it will be his last meal.
- Inshallah.
What's happening?
Are you okay?
Do you hear me?
Thank you, buddy, both for the
ayran (a Turkish drink) and...
your clothes.
Can you just...--
Go, now.
We'll talk to Bamsı Bey.
Sons.
Bamsı Bey...
Tell me now.
Where do we go first?
To who?
Do you know where to go, Osman Bey?
We'll go to your father, Ertuğrul Ghazi.
Osman.
He is the Bey of Kayı.
Osman wouldn't let
Savcı and Dündar to be Beys.
- Are you surprised?
- Petros.
Of course, no.
So, Dündar Bey betrayed Savcı.
And Savcı betrayed Dündar Bey.
And Osman became Bey.
What are you thinking, Petros?
To kill two birds with one stone.
Maybe three.
Maybe five.
We'll not only destroy Osman's reputation
with the stones we throw...
but also, we'll give
opportunity to Dündar...
who wants something else.
So?
We'll make Dündar collaborate with us.
How?
That's my job.
My brother.
Do you think they can finish Osman?
They'll try, Helen.
Let them try.
Okay, Vladius...
- Can they really do it?
- They'll try Helen!
I just thought that they may have a man
in Kayı tribe.
Of course, Helen.
Of course they may have.
I am sure they have a man here too.
The real issue is not that. What concerns
us is the question: What are they after?
This is the problem.
I want to figure this out.
Besides, it is really noteworthy that they
have come here in the time of election.
What happens when there is an election,
Helen?
- Someone take over the throne.
- Just that?
Some other things change as well.
So they have come here for
"some other things."
So Turks have secret plans too.
I'm not proud of it, but I also love
to have secret plans.
Osman Bey, I have a secret.
A secret that should be known only by you.
No one else is to known.
This is why I am explaining this to you.
This is Ertugrul Ghazi's heritage.
It's his relics.
Didn't we get all the relics today,
Bamsı Bey?
These are other relics, Osman Bey.
These are relics that have come down to
Kayı Beys from Turkish rulers.
These are almighty relics.
Why did I not know that before?
Osman Bey, if you hadn't been selected
as a Bey...
you wouldn't know it now.
Because these relics are handed
Beys to Beys.
When can I see?
Let's not waste time.
Let's depart.
Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com